Guide to the Cornell University News Service records, [ca. 1920s-2000s].
Cornell University News Service records
- Series VI. Cornell University News Services records, 1920s-2000s
  - Press Releases, News Clippings, Distribution Lists, Administrative Files, Subject Files
    - Alumni Subject File
      - Alumni - O, Mary Anne Ocampo, Lawrence Osa-Afiana, Perry D.Odak, George Odden, Dede Oetomo, Joe O'Hara, William O. Lay, Vicki A. O'Meara, Stewart O'Nan, Matthew Opel, Melissa Bank, Michael Ross, Agda S. Osborn, Stuart I. Oran, Douglas D. Osheroff, and Nathaniel Owings (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 28)
      - Alumni - Ohrabach, Jerome K. (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 29)
      - Alumni - Olbermann, Keith (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 30)
      - Alumni - Ottinger, Richard L. (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 31)
      - Alumni - P, Lance Peters, Bryan Pease, Alan Paller, R. R. Palmer, Edward L. Palmer, Robert S. Palmer, Fred D. Parris, Anne Paoletti, Paolucci, Kathleen Parthe, Gregory Pass, Mitchell Fredrick Paster, Stephan Paternot, Janet Reno, Marsha J. Pechman, James Peddi, John H. Pedersen, Anthony D. Pellegrini, Christine Pelvecchio, Mike Pennell, Laurence T. Penny, Robert Perciasepe, Frances Perkins, Lisa Perrin, Helen Stone Peterson, Jay Petri, George R. Pfann, Pete Pfitzinger, Samuel Pierce, Francis M. Piphin, Sam Pizzigati, Charles Platkins, Lewis E. Platt, Stephen A. Ploscowe, Antonio Poglianich, Michael Polk, Michael Polk, Edward Pollak, Apinan Poshyananda, Martin Powell, Dave Price, Richard Price, Aric Press, May Preston, Louis J. 'Dusty' Profumo, Sharon Prost, and Thomas Pynchon (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 32)
      - Alumni - Paternot, Stephan (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 33)
      - Alumni - Paxton Jr., James L. (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 34)
      - Alumni - Peters, Tom (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 35)
      - Alumni - Philips, Ellis L. (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 36)
      - Alumni - Pierce Jr., Samuel R. (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 37)
      - Alumni - Pohl, Otto (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 38)
      - Alumni - Pogue, Richard W. (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 39)
      - Alumni - Pollitt, Daniel H. (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 40)
      - Alumni - Pollock, Lawrence (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 41)
      - Alumni - Polzer Jr., George F. (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 42)
      - Alumni - Price, Robert D. (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 43)
      - Alumni - Q, Damion Quaye and Maureen Quigley (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 44)
      - Alumni - R, Jennifer J. Raab, Vicky Romanoff, Jeff Rackow, Atif Rafay, Tage J. Rainsford, Dan Ralph, Randal, Justin Rattner, Ted Rauch, Bruce S. Raynor, Robert J. Raymond, Hawk Reherman, Robert Reich, Margaret Reed, Don Reeves, Simon Reich, Steve Reich, Naomi Remen, Janet Reno, Henry S. Reuss, Elizabeth Reveal, Alister W. Reynolds, Harriet Lange Rheingold, Harold Rice, Christopher Rich, Anne Louise Roehrig Rideout, Jeffrey Riedl, Kenneth W. Rind, Stephen C. Robinson, Aubrey Eugene Robinson Jr., John Rodewig, Robert L. Rogers, Clark T. Rogerson, Ben Rogoff, Joseph A. Rokovich, Calvin W. Rolark, David Romm, Myron Roomkin, Richard RosenbaumDavid Rosengarten, Lucinda Rosenfeld, Jay Rosenkrantz, Bernie Rosner, Michael Ross, Amy Ross, Dave Ross, Michael Ross, Catherine Ross, Judith A. Rossiter, Caleb Rossiter, Clinton Rossiter, Andrew Rossner, Don H. Rotenberg, Susan Roth, Laura Riding, Christopher Rouse, Rubenstein, Nathan Rudgers, Thomas Russo, Mark Rust, Steve Ryan, and Robert Rymer (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 45)
      - Alumni - Rabi, Isidor Isaac (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 46)
      - Alumni - Redington, Rowland W. (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 47)
      - Alumni - Reeve, Christopher (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 48)
      - Alumni - Reich, Steven (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 49)
      - Alumni - Reid, Graig (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 50)
      - Alumni - Reno, Janet (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 51)
      - Alumni - Rogers, William P. (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 52)
      - Alumni - Roberts, Steven J. (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 53)
      - Alumni - Robeson Jr., Paul (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 54)
      - Alumni - Roseman, Marina (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 55)
      - Alumni - Rosenbaum, Richard (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 56)
      - Alumni - Roth, Nelson E. (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 57)
      - Alumni - Rubinstein, Jon (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 58)
      - Alumni - Ruff, Matt (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 59)
      - Alumni - S, Joseph Sabga, Bruce Sachs, Edward Swenson, Julie Anne Sadie, Daniel E. Salmon, Miriam M. Salpeter, Nick Salvatore, Frank A. Santamaria, Donna Sapolin, Vicki Saporta, Jack Sarfatti, Malinia Saval, Monique Savarese, Paul Sayvetz, Louis P. Scafuri, Dick Schaap, Lewis G. Schaeneman, Jr., Cindy Schlaepfer, Jill Schensul, Carole Schiffman, David Schild, Scott Schiller, Rudolf Schlesinger, Todd H. Schliemann, Stephen E. Schneider, Allen Schoen, Thelma Schoonmaker, Schrader, James L. Schram, William L. Schrader, Laurie Shulman, Mark Schultz, Dick Schwartz, John J. Schwartz, Michael Schwerner, Jim Seay, Cynthia Secor, Stephen R. Sestanovich, John Sewell, Naren Shankar, Sumner Sharpe, Perry Shaul, Melville ShavelsonHolly R. Sheffield, Paul Sheridan, Brian Sheils, Kristin Schiesswohl, Jack Shirman, John W. Shively, Judy Shulewitz, Jon Shure, Isabelle Stone, Thomas Silliman, William Simon, Daniel Simpkins, Paul Sinal, Steven Sinofsky, Daniel G. Sisler, Richard Sklar, Stephen Skowronek, Neil Sloane, Perry D. Slocum, Robert Smigel, David Smith, Helen Elliott Belding Smith, David Smith, Kimberley A. Smith, Jane B. Smith, Jimmy Smits, Daniel Snowman, Phillip Snyder, Steven E. Snyder, Joel Seligman, Stephen Snyder, Jay Solomon, Fred J. Solowey, Norman M. Some, Fred Somkin, Frederick Sommer, Suman Sorg, Mary Ann Sovocool, Thomas Sowell, Warren M. Sperry, Clarence Spicer, Jay Spiegel, Gayatri Spivak, Warren Staley, Wanda Stambaugh, Christopher Stearns, Richard Edmund Stearns, Sharon Stein, Jacob Steinberg, Sean Steinwald, Andrew Sterge, Judith Stewart, Terry Stewart, George Robert Stibitz, Susan Stiles, William C. Stokoe Jr., Phillip Stambaugh, Robert P. Story, Tracy Stouffer, Roger A. Strauch, Michael Strauss, William Strunk Jr., Larry Sugar, Arudoudebito Sugawara, Kathleen M. Sullivan, William C. Summers, John Conrad Swartz Jr., paul Szasz, Jan Švejnar, Amanda Sauer, and Susan Sheridan (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 60)
      - Alumni - Saporta, Vicki A. (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 61)
      - Alumni - Savage, Jay (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 62)
      - Alumni - Schaaff, Charles H. (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 63)
      - Alumni - Schaap, Richard J. (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 64)
      - Alumni - Scheverner, Michael (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 65)
      - Alumni - Schimmel, Edward (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 66)
      - Alumni - Schlichting, Nancy (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 67)
      - Alumni - Schmitt, Max F. (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 68)
      - Alumni - Schoellkopf, Jacob F. (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 69)
      - Alumni - Schoellkorf, Paul A. (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 70)
      - Alumni - Schrader, William (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 71)
      - Alumni - Sears-Collins, Leah J. (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 72)
      - Alumni - Shapiro, Phil (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 73)
      - Alumni - Shavelson, Melville (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 74)
      - Alumni - Sheinkman, Jack (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 75)
      - Alumni - Shulman, Ellen L. (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 76)
      - Alumni - Silbert, Joseph (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 77)
      - Alumni - Singer, Alex (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 78)
      - Alumni - Singer, Michael (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 79)
      - Alumni - Sister Souljah (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 80)
      - Alumni - Smith, Tony (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 81)
      - Alumni - Smith, William A. III (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 82)
      - Alumni - Smits, Jimmy (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 83)
      - Alumni - Smoke, Ed (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 84)
      - Alumni - Sowell, Thomas (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 85)
      - Alumni - Spillman, Robert A. (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 86)
      - Alumni - Springer II, Lewis E. (Box 4-3-15 - 155, Folder 87)
      - Alumni - Stamp, Al. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 1)
      - Alumni - Stephenson, Holly H. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 2)
      - Alumni - Sternberg, Connie (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 3)
      - Alumni - Stocker, James (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 4)
      - Alumni - Sturdy, Howard Henry (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 5)
      - Alumni - Sullivan Jr., John (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 6)
      - Alumni - Swanson, Lynne (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 7)
      - Alumni - T, Philip Taietz, Ted Teng, Ellen Talmage, Larry Tanenbaum, Ching Tang, Stephen D. Tannen, Ratan Tata, Lee Teng-hui, Tauriel, Joseph Taubman, Todd Taylor, John Q. Teare, Patricia Tengel, Ralph S. Terkowitz, Melanie Thernstrom, Andrea Thies, Heinn F. Tomfohrde, Robert L. Thompson Jr., John Thorbjarnarson, Lorraine Power Tharp, Catherine Tingey, Jennifer Tipton, James Tisch, Andrew Tisch, Joan Nesmith Tillotson, Olive Tjaden Van Sickle, Francis William Tomasic, Fred Tomczyk, Robert Traub, Patrick Thean, Janet Travell, William Trenchard, Hugh Troy, John C. Truesdale, Ming Tsai, Paul Tsui, Donald Turcotte, Helen Turley, Wallace Rupert Turnbull, and Winfield W. Tyler (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 8)
      - Alumni - Tarter, Jill Cornell (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 9)
      - Alumni - Tanner, Mike (Deceased) (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 10)
      - Alumni - Tewey, John F. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 11)
      - Alumni - Thernstrom, Melanie (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 12)
      - Alumni - Thompson, David D. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 13)
      - Alumni - Trequrtha, Paul R. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 14)
      - Alumni - Treman Jr., Charles E. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 15)
      - Alumni - Tucker, Richard F. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 16)
      - Alumni - Tumenggung, Syafruddin (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 17)
      - Alumni - U, Isamu Ueda, Maxwell Mayhew Upson, and Matthew Urban (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 18)
      - Alumni - Urban, Matthew (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 19)
      - Alumni - V, Rebecca A. Vallely, Karen G. Venezky, Bradd Vickers, Kevin Vigilante, Barbara J. B. Vogel, Paula Vogel, Leslie Voltaire, Matthew Von, and Sandra Vafelgesang (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 20)
      - Alumni - W, Alfred Watts, Sanford Weill, Sandy Weill, Lauren Weisberger, Chan Wai Leong, Karen Lee Wald, Pete Wakeman, Laura Wakeman, Jay Walker, Robert Walker, Ken Walkup, William Wallance, Dennis P. Walsh, Koigi wa Wamwere, Heather MacLean Walters, Dazong Wang, Andrea Wasserman, Nach Waxman, Steven Weinberg, John Thomas Weeker, Sebela Wehe, Neil Weinfield, Larry Weissman, Mary-Scott Welch, William Wenck, Richard Wesley, Richard Wesley, Paul Wheaton, Ellen Kuney Whetzel, Mark Whitacre, Michele Whitham, E. B. White, Robert Franklin White, John White, John P. White, Richard H. White, Michelle Wieghart, Eliot Wigginton, Jesse Wigutow, L. John Wilkerson, Antoinette Miele Wilkinson, Charles Wille, Buffy Williams, Katie Williams, Barry william, Brackette F. Williams, L. Pearce Williams, Lisa Williamson, Leslie A. Williamson, Paul Kelsey Williams, Jan Willis, Joseph Wilson, Patrick D. Wilson, Kenneth E. Wing, Jeffrey K. Winikow, Elmer Woelffer, David Wolf, Spencer Wolf, Paul Wolfowitz, Howard Wolfson, Robert L. Wolke, Gary Wood, Frank Wood, Miriam Woolfolk, Peter E. Wright, Ron D. Wright, Sheryl Wudunn, and Susan Davenny Wyner (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 21)
      - Alumni - Wallace, Frank (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 22)
      - Alumni - Weinberg, Steven (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 23)
      - Alumni - Weintrab, Bernard A. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 24)
      - Alumni - Weiss, Roger J. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 25)
      - Alumni - Werly, Charles M. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 26)
      - Alumni - Whitacre, Mark (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 27)
      - Alumni - White, E. B. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 28)
      - Alumni - Wiggins, Bruce (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 29)
      - Alumni - Wilson, Carlton P. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 30)
      - Alumni - Withrow, James (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 31)
      - Alumni - Wolfowitz, Paul D. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 32)
      - Alumni - Wolfson, Edward A. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 33)
      - Alumni - Wright, Irving S. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 34)
      - Alumni - Wruble, Brian F. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 35)
      - Alumni - Wudunn, Sheryl (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 36)
      - Alumni - Y, Kozo Yamamoto, Peter Yarrow, Edward Young, and David Yewell (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 37)
      - Alumni - Z, Peter Zahler, Andrew Zepp, Albert Francis Zahm, Ilir Zherka, Howard Zibel, Donald Zinn, and Andrew Zuckerman (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 38)
      - Alumni - Zelnick, Bob (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 39)
      - Alumni - Zimmer, Orpha Spicer (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 40)
      - Alumni - Feeney, Charles F. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 41)
    - Trustee Subject Files
      - Trustees - Affinito, Lilyan H. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 42)
      - Trustees - Barber, Rober J. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 43)
      - Trustees - Berens, Donald P. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 44)
      - Trustees - Bibliowicz, Jessica (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 45)
      - Trustees - Bitz, Robert W. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 46)
      - Trustees - Boand, Catherine Bard (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 47)
      - Trustees - Abrams, Robert H. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 48)
      - Trustees - Trustees 1999 Presentation (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 49)
      - Trustees - Call, Richard C. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 50)
      - Trustees - Chang, Gordon G. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 51)
      - Trustees - Christian, Mary T. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 52)
      - Trustees - Cisler, Walker L. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 53)
      - Trustees - Clark, James M. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 54)
      - Trustees - Clark, Thomas J. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 55)
      - Trustees - Cleary, Edward J. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 56)
      - Trustees - Cohen, Abby Joseph (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 57)
      - Trustees - Conable, Barber (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 58)
      - Trustees - Conable, Charlotte W. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 59)
      - Trustees - Corbett, Raymond R. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 60)
      - Trustees - Cowie, Robert A. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 61)
      - Trustees - Culbertson, David J. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 62)
      - Trustees - Dealy, Katie (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 63)
      - Trustees - Derr, Kenneth T. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 64)
      - Trustees - Dyson, John S. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 65)
      - Trustees - Engel, Robert G. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 66)
      - Trustees - Falvey, Mary (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 67)
      - Trustees - Ferguson, Glenn (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 68)
      - Trustees - Johnson, H. Fisk (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 69)
      - Trustees - Flanigan, Horice C. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 70)
      - Trustees - Flansburgh, E. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 71)
      - Trustees - Flansburgh, Earl R. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 72)
      - Trustees - Friedman, Barbara (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 73)
      - Trustees - Gibbs Jr., James L. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 74)
      - Trustees - Grohmann, Victor H. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 75)
      - Trustees - Holland, Jerome H. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 76)
      - Trustees - Hollander, Louis (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 77)
      - Trustees - Inumaru, Ichiro (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 78)
      - Trustees - Johnson, Herbert F. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 79)
      - Trustees - Johnson, Samuel C. (Box 4-3-15 - 156, Folder 80)
      - Trustees - Jones, Tom (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 1)
      - Trustees - Kinxelberg, Harvey (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 2)
      - Trustees - Knight, Charles F. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 3)
      - Trustees - Knight, John S. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 4)
      - Trustees - Knight Jr., Lester B. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 5)
      - Trustees - Lake Jr., Charles W. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 6)
      - Trustees - Lee, Charles R. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 7)
      - Trustees - Levin, William A. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 8)
      - Trustees - Loeb, Frances L. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 9)
      - Trustees - Linowitz, Sol (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 10)
      - Trustees - Lynch, Ronald P. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 11)
      - Trustees - Manchester Jr., Eli (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 12)
      - Trustees - Marshall, Dale Rogers (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 13)
      - Trustees - McDonald, R.J. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 14)
      - Trustees - Meinig, Peter C. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 15)
      - Trustees - Menschel, Ronay (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 16)
      - Trustees - Meredith, Denise (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 17)
      - Trustees - Merrill, Philip (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 18)
      - Trustees - Mitchell, Albert R. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 19)
      - Trustees - Milstein, Howard P. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 20)
      - Trustees - Molisani, Howard E. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 21)
      - Trustees - Neafsey, John P. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 22)
      - Trustees - Newbury, George A. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 23)
      - Trustees - Newman, Floyd R. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 24)
      - Trustees - Noyes, Jansen Jr. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 25)
      - Trustees - Olin, John M. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 26)
      - Trustees - Osborne Jr., Stanley D. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 27)
      - Trustees - Osmer-Mcquade, Margaret (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 28)
      - Trustees - Paul, Eve Weinsch (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 29)
      - Trustees - Pederson, Ronald W. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 30)
      - Trustees - Peter, George (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 31)
      - Trustees - Pfann, George R. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 32)
      - Trustees - Platt, Robert C. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 33)
      - Trustees - Plowe, Christopher (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 34)
      - Trustees - Pollak, David (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 35)
      - Trustees - Potter, Bernard W. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 36)
      - Trustees - Procope, Ernesta G. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 37)
      - Trustees - Purcell, Robert W. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 38)
      - Trustees - Raynor, Bruce (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 39)
      - Trustees - Rebmann Jr., Ruthland G. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 40)
      - Trustees - Ridgley, Robert L. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 41)
      - Trustees - Roberts, Lillian (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 42)
      - Trustees - Robertson, William R. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 43)
      - Trustees - Robinson, Aubrey E. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 44)
      - Trustees - Robison, Ellis H. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 45)
      - Trustees - Rogers, Adele L. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 46)
      - Trustees - Rosenbaum, Robin (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 47)
      - Trustees - Sampson, Harvey (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 48)
      - Trustees - Saperston, Alfred M. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 49)
      - Trustees - Schaenen Jr., Netson (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 50)
      - Trustees - Schoales, Dudley N. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 51)
      - Trustees - Schoonover, Jean W. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 52)
      - Trustees - Schwartz, Richard J. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 53)
      - Trustees - Scruggs, Frank P. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 54)
      - Trustees - Severinghaus, Leslie R. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 55)
      - Trustees - Sheinkman, Jacob (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 56)
      - Trustees - Slocum, George S. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 57)
      - Trustees - Stevens, Stoddard M. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 58)
      - Trustees - Stewart, Charles T. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 59)
      - Trustees - Stewart, Patricia (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 60)
      - Trustees - Tanner, Harold (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 61)
      - Trustees - Ten-Eyck, Peter (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 62)
      - Trustees - Ward, Carlton J. Jr. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 63)
      - Trustees - Weill, Sanford (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 64)
      - Trustees - Wickham, Don J. (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 65)
      - Trustees - Widger, Bruce (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 66)
      - Trustees - Williams, Kenneth (Box 4-3-15 - 157, Folder 67)
    - Faculty Subject Files
      - Faculty - Abowd, John Maron (Box 4-3-15 - 158, Folder 1)
      - Faculty - Abrams, Barbara (Box 4-3-15 - 158, Folder 2)
      - Faculty - Abrams, Kathryn (Box 4-3-15 - 158, Folder 3)
      - Faculty - Abruna, Hector D. (Box 4-3-15 - 158, Folder 4)
      - Faculty - Acland, Gregory (Box 4-3-15 - 158, Folder 5)
      - Faculty - Acree, Terry (Box 4-3-15 - 158, Folder 6)
      - Faculty - Adkins-Regan, Elizabeth (Box 4-3-15 - 158, Folder 7)
      - Faculty - Adler, Kraig (Box 4-3-15 - 158, Folder 8)
      - Faculty - Aguirre, Gustavo D. (Box 4-3-15 - 158, Folder 9)
      - Faculty - Albright, Louis D. (Box 4-3-15 - 158, Folder 10)
      - Faculty - Alexander, Martin (Box 4-3-15 - 158, Folder 11)
      - Faculty - Altschuler, Gleen Craig (Box 4-3-15 - 158, Folder 12)
      - Faculty - Anderson, Benedict (Box 4-3-15 - 158, Folder 13)
      - Faculty - Anderson, Carol L. (Box 4-3-15 - 158, Folder 14)
      - Faculty - Antczak, D. F. (Box 4-3-15 - 158, Folder 15)
      - Faculty - Apsel, Alyssa (Box 4-3-15 - 158, Folder 16)
      - Faculty - Aquadro, Charles F. (Box 4-3-15 - 158, Folder 17)
      - Faculty - Arbel, Avner (Box 4-3-15 - 158, Folder 18)
      - Faculty - Arntzen, Charles (Box 4-3-15 - 158, Folder 19)
      - Faculty - Arntzen, Charles J. (Box 4-3-15 - 158, Folder 20)
      - Faculty - Ashcroft, Neil W. (Box 4-3-15 - 158, Folder 21)
      - Faculty - Ashdown, Susan (Box 4-3-15 - 158, Folder 22)
      - Faculty - Avery, Robert (Box 4-3-15 - 159, Folder 1)
      - Faculty - Avery, Rosemary Jane (Box 4-3-15 - 159, Folder 2)
      - Faculty - Bacharach, Samuel R. (Box 4-3-15 - 159, Folder 3)
      - Faculty - Bailey, Warren (Box 4-3-15 - 159, Folder 4)
      - Faculty - Bain, Mark (Box 4-3-15 - 159, Folder 5)
      - Faculty - Baird, Barbara A. (Box 4-3-15 - 159, Folder 6)
      - Faculty - Ballantyne, Joseph M. (Box 4-3-15 - 159, Folder 7)
      - Faculty - Bandler, David K. (Box 4-3-15 - 159, Folder 8)
      - Faculty - Barazangi, Nimat Hafez (Box 4-3-15 - 159, Folder 9)
      - Faculty - Barazangi, Muawia (Box 4-3-15 - 159, Folder 10)
      - Faculty - Barbano, David M. (Box 4-3-15 - 159, Folder 11)
      - Faculty - Barreiro, Jose (Box 4-3-15 - 159, Folder 12)
      - Faculty - Barrett, Christopher (Box 4-3-15 - 159, Folder 13)
      - Faculty - Barry, Frank D. (Box 4-3-15 - 159, Folder 14)
      - Faculty - Bartel, Donald L. (Box 4-3-15 - 159, Folder 15)
      - Faculty - Bass, Andrew (Box 4-3-15 - 159, Folder 16)
      - Faculty - Bassuk, Nina (Box 4-3-15 - 159, Folder 17)
      - Faculty - Batt, Carl A. (Box 4-3-15 - 160, Folder 1)
      - Faculty - Bauman, Dale (Box 4-3-15 - 160, Folder 2)
      - Faculty - Bauman, Dale (Box 4-3-15 - 160, Folder 3)
      - Faculty - Becker, Franklin D. (Box 4-3-15 - 160, Folder 4)
      - Faculty - Beer, Steven V. (Box 4-3-15 - 160, Folder 5)
      - Faculty - Beerman, Donald (Box 4-3-15 - 160, Folder 6)
      - Faculty - Bell, James (Box 4-3-15 - 160, Folder 7)
      - Faculty - Belzer, Michael (Box 4-3-15 - 160, Folder 8)
      - Faculty - Bem, Daryl (Box 4-3-15 - 160, Folder 9)
      - Faculty - Bendaniel, David J. (Box 4-3-15 - 160, Folder 10)
      - Faculty - Bergstrom, Gary C. (Box 4-3-15 - 160, Folder 11)
      - Faculty - Bem, Sandra L. (Box 4-3-15 - 160, Folder 12)
      - Faculty - Bernal, Martin (Box 4-3-15 - 160, Folder 13)
      - Faculty - Bethe, Hans (Box 4-3-15 - 160, Folder 14)
      - Faculty - Beyenbach, Klaus (Box 4-3-15 - 161, Folder 1)
      - Faculty - Bierman, Harold (Box 4-3-15 - 161, Folder 2)
      - Faculty - Bilderback, Donald (Box 4-3-15 - 161, Folder 3)
      - Faculty - Bills, Nelson L. (Box 4-3-15 - 161, Folder 4)
      - Faculty - Bilson, Malcolm (Box 4-3-15 - 161, Folder 5)
      - Faculty - Bishop, John H. (Box 4-3-15 - 161, Folder 6)
      - Faculty - Bishop, Jonathan P. (Box 4-3-15 - 161, Folder 7)
      - Faculty - Blau, Francine D. (Box 4-3-15 - 161, Folder 8)
      - Faculty - Blass, Elliot M. (Box 4-3-15 - 161, Folder 9)
      - Faculty - Bloomfield, Robert (Box 4-3-15 - 161, Folder 10)